promarket.in 2011-11-06

# Privacy policy

## What personal data is needed

We collect personal information: name, surname, name of the company, company details, contact numbers, e-mail address, address of the company. Also we might ask for another information: 

  * Cookies to determine the browser of the user and render services depending on this option, for example, saving of the data in the recycle bin between the visits 
  * IP-address of the user to show advertisements 
  * info about the errors on the website
  * behavior of the user on the website 

All information is collected in original form. 

## Information about you will be used by the company

We may use your name, surname, e-mail address, password for identification you as a user ProMarket.in. We may display name, surname, name of the company, company details, contact numbers, e-mail address, address of the company on ProMarket.in.   
We may use your contact information to send you information about new opportunities, promos and other news on ProMarket.in. User can always unsubscribe from such notifications in the corresponding section of My Account. 

## How does the company pass information to the third parties 

We do not pass any information to the third parties with personal information, except cases when the third party renders a service, such as handling of payments or delivery. Third parties may use personal information only in case of rendering the service and only information required for rendering a service. 

## How to edit/delete information or unsubscribe from subscription

Users can edit/delete their personal information whenever they want to or unsubscribe from the subscription. For doing this they just need to go to My Account. Functioning of certain possibilities of ProMarket.in that require personal information can be stopped since information has been edited/deleted. 

## Contact address for business in case the questions will rise 

In case any questions, requests, complaints concerning information you provide will rise, please, contact us: support@promarket.in, Boryspilska str, 9, building 91, office 107, Kyiv, Ukraine, 02660. 

## Protection of collected information

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us. All data we collect is stored on one or more protected database servers that are not accessible other than from the corporate network. Only those workers of the company who need access to the personal data have information about the users. All workers who have access to the personal data have signed the non-disclosure agreement. 

## Changes in privacy policy 

We can change the terms of the privacy policy. In this case we will change the page on the terms page. Please, periodically look these terms carefully through, for being informed about the ways of ProMarket.in to protect information about the users. 

## Privacy policy

Description of the privacy policy <http://promarket.in/privacy-policy> is on http://promarket.in/privacy_policy
